Contact

princemjy998@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/prince-johnson-64250819b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Web Development Django

Game Development

Certifications

Introduction to Game Developement
Principles of Game Design
Badgets and Labs

Become A Full Stack Web Developer - Beginner To Advanced

Game Development for Modern

Honors-Awards

Platforms

Google Kick Start Round E

Prince Johnson

Student at Cochin University of Science and Technology Kottarakara

Summary

Experienced Web Designer with a demonstrated history of working in the internet industry. Skilled in C#, Ethical Hacking, Bootstrap, C, and HTML5. Strong arts and design professional with a Bachelor of Technology - BTech focused in Computer Science from Cochin University of Science and Technology.

Experience

Banzan Ventures
Game Programmer
July 2020 - Present (2 months)
Kochi, Kerala, India

Internshala

6 months

Internshala Student Partner 18 May 2020 - August 2020 (4 months)

Ethical Hacking March 2020 - May 2020 (3 months) India

Networkz Systems Summer Intern June 2019 - August 2019 (3 months) Kollam, Kerala, India

Web Developement Internship in Python
Designed a Web developement project in Django

Networkz Systems
Summer Intern
June 2018 - July 2018 (2 months)

Kollam, Kerala

Core Java Developement

Designed a GUI interface web-application project

Education

Cochin University of Science and Technology

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (2017 - 2021)

St Antony's Public School
(2015 - 2017)